{
    "subject": "resource/Battle_of_Gdynia",
    "predicate": "ontology/commander",
    "object": "resource/Fedor_von_Bock",
    "human_readable": "The commander of the Battle of Gdynia was Fedor von Bock.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9155089259147644,
            "question": "Who commanded the Battle of Gdynia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9029256105422974,
            "question": "What battle did Fedor von Bock command?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8406897783279419,
            "question": "Was Fedor von Bock a military commander?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8323422074317932,
            "question": "Name a battle led by Fedor von Bock."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5652106404304504,
            "question": "What is the significance of the Battle of Gdynia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5561457872390747,
            "question": "Who were the opposing forces in the Battle of Gdynia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5353618264198303,
            "question": "When did the Battle of Gdynia occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5329932570457458,
            "question": "In what historical event was Fedor von Bock involved?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4789426028728485,
            "question": "Where did the Battle of Gdynia take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39872410893440247,
            "question": "What were Fedor von Bock's military strategies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The commander of the Battle of Gdynia was Fedor von Bock.",
            "html": "dbpedia_597_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did the Battle of Gdynia take place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_597_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what historical event was Fedor von Bock involved?",
            "html": "dbpedia_597_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did the Battle of Gdynia occur?",
            "html": "dbpedia_597_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_597_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_597_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_597_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_597_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_597_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_597_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_597_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_597_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_597_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_597_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that Fedor von Bock commanded Army Group North during the Invasion of Poland in 1939, they do not specify him as the commander of the Battle of Gdynia.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while Fedor von Bock is mentioned in several documents as a German military commander, there is no mention of him being involved in the Battle of Gdynia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention Fedor von Bock being the commander of the Battle of Gdynia. The information provided talks about his command roles in various campaigns and battles such as the Invasion of Poland, Invasion of France, attack on the Soviet Union, and Army Group South during World War II. There is no reference to him commanding the Battle of Gdynia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Fedor von Bock is not known to have commanded the Battle of Gdynia specifically, as his notable campaigns include the invasion of Poland and the Battle of France, but there is no mention or evidence that he led the Battle of Gdynia in the provided context.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "None of the provided text mentions Fedor von Bock being involved in or commanding the Battle of Gdynia.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Fedor von Bock was the commander of Army Group North during the Invasion of Poland, but there is no mention of him being involved in a specific battle at Gdynia. The context information does not provide any evidence that he led forces at the Battle of Gdynia.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Fedor von Bock commanding the Battle of Gdynia in the provided context. The information focuses on his roles during other major campaigns such as the Invasion of Poland, Invasion of France, and the battles on the Eastern Front, but does not include any reference to a Battle of Gdynia.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}